hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Shikamaru always believed in me...
More than myself or Neji or
any of us here... He is stronger!
Let's go, fatso!
Don't you say that!
Partial Expansion Jutsu...
Arm!
Leg!
Partial Expansion Jutsu...
Arm!
Don't mess with me! Scum!
Eat this!
What!
Super Expansion Jutsu!
Goodbye
My Friend...!
Even So, I Believe
I did it... Shikamaru...
What?!
I can't believe I had to get to
the second state
for an opponent like this one...
Slamming Palm!
What... What is that appearance?!
Now that it's come to this it's over.
In the second state I can put out ten times
more power than I have thus far.
I'm invincible.
It's too painful to move...
Who knew that the side effects
of the Curry Pill would be this intense.
This is what happens...
to a powerless scum for butting in!
Playing Ninja better suits you!
Raise your hand if you're playing Ninja.
Wait...
Rock, paper... scissors!
Split!
One, two, three...
W-Wait!
99... 100!
Hey! I said split!
Ouch!
Found you!
Give up quietly the two of you!
We finally caught 'em!
I'm sick of this!
The team with Choji always loses!
Sorry...
I need a lot of Chakra
for this "second state."
I'll take whatever Chakra
you have left!
Well then, I'll take them now.
There's not much left...
You're empty!
I haven't had nearly enough to eat...
I said I haven't had enough to eat!
Huh...?
What just one last piece, huh...
When I said I haven't had
enough to eat...
Just as I thought you're the scum
used as a sacrificial pawn.
Die... you pitiful fatso the odd man out.
I won't let you play Ninja with us!
Why?
Because if we let you play
we'll lose.
You're slow.
Yeah but... then the number
of people won't be even.
Shogi is fun
because the number of pieces are even.
A piece that is useless is
the same as not having that piece!
Yeah, that's right!
We're the ones with fewer people
and we're not complaining.
Hurry up, let's do it!
If it's okay with you then it's fine...
Okay, it's settled!
We can win it!
Yes!
Where are we gonna hide this time?
And um, the whole Akimichi Clan
is fat and slow...
That's what everyone says.
Really...
But Choji you're a kindhearted guy...
more than everyone else.
One day you'll surely make friends
who'll see that quality of yours.
And then you should cherish
those friends
and be the kind of friends
who believe in each other...
Can I really make... friends like that...
someone like me...?
Rest in peace...
you're not the only one
I'm going to get.
After I kill you,
I'm going to get the cruel sleazy
mean guys who used you as a sacrifice!
Because he... promised...
You better catch up with us... Choji.
Okay!
He's definitely going to defeat
the opponent and come after us...!
Yep!
That's right... he can do it.
Okay! While I'm here...
Me too...
All right everyone,
we get Sasuke back
before Choji catches up!
Wait!
All right! Here we come!
He's late... that Jirobo...
He's greedy and eats so much...
He's probably squeezing out Chakra
even from the marrow of their bones.
I wish he had switched
with me already...
Here I'll give it back!
Well then...
If I linger
I won't be able to catch up.
It's about time to put an end to this.
The Chili Pepper Pill is left...
But... if I take that...
I'll die without a doubt...
Don't you dare die, Choji...
We've been doing things together
since that day...
Oh...! You...
You... were there just now...
What about playing Ninja?
It was a drag
so I pulled myself out from it.
Huh...?
By the way that's my special seat.
Your special seat?
I like to lie on my back and
look at the clouds on a nice day like this.
You've come to look at clouds?
Mind if I sit there?
Oh... sure!
This is a good place.
You can see the clouds well.
Yeah...
Why don't you...
What...?
watch the clouds with me
and lounge around?
Okay!
You know! I-I brought snacks.
Want some?
Oh, that'd be great!
Thanks.
Eating potato chips
while watching clouds... this is the best.
Yep!
My name is Shikamaru...
from the Nara Clan.
You... What's your name?
It's Choji! Akimichi Choji
of the Akimichi Clan!
Choji, huh...
I think I'll get along with you.
Me too!
We'll always do things together
from now on too.
Choji...!
Shikamaru... Sorry... I can't go...
It's over...
But this guy...
I have to beat him...
even if it means death.
No matter what you do now
it's too late!
Crushing Palm!
Wh-What's that...?
But...
Boulder Blow!
It's no good!
I'm 100 times stronger than before!
They say that food
can be a reason
for people to hold a horrible grudge
against somebody.
The blow just now...
was for eating the last bite of my snack...
No way!
This guy has so much Chakra that
his body has changed physically!
And this is...
for making fun of me by calling me
a sacrificial pawn and fat!
But what I can't forgive you for
more than anything else...
You sure do suffer when
you have a stupid leader. You underlings!
Well... I'll kill you losers
before you suffer working
under a glum shadow lover like him!
You should blame your stupid leader
for choosing you!
You insulted my best friend!
More than mocking me
by calling me fat
and poaching the last bite
of a four-star meal...
I can't forgive you for that!
All of my Chakra... to my left hand!
Uh uh-oh...!
This blow... is heavier than my life!
W-Wait...! Don't be hasty...!
I... I won.
Me... I won!
Everyone...
But Choji...
you're a kindhearted guy
more than everyone else...
One day you'll surely make friends
who'll see that part of you...
And then you should cherish
those friends
and be the kind of friends
who believe in each other.
"Hurry up and get over here."
It's Naruto.
"Everyone's waiting."
Kiba...
Shikamaru...
Ino-Shika-Cho!
Even if it is just potato chips
I won't let anybody else have
the last piece no matter who you are.
Choji and I have worked as a team
for many years
so coordinating with him
is easiest for me.
Dad...
I've made... a lot of friends...
What happened?
Nothin'...
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Take this!
Fang Over Fang!
Byakugan!
That damn spider bastard!
Me, Naruto, Kiba and Neji.
Our careful planning is not working!
If we waste time, Sasuke will be gone!
Hey, what should we do?!
If we want to continue our pursuit
there's only one way to do it!
Next time:
"Your Opponent is me!"